<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome on James Tombleson</title><link>https://www.jamestombleson.com/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome on James Tombleson</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 21:13:30 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jamestombleson.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it time to Go?</title><link>https://www.jamestombleson.com/posts/2023/02/25/is-it-time-to-go/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 21:13:30 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.jamestombleson.com/posts/2023/02/25/is-it-time-to-go/</guid><description>I will have been working with go for a year next month. This last year I have learned so much about the language and come to love how simple and flexible it is. I see a great future for it within the web ecosystem. It&amp;rsquo;s very easy to build up a new web service in go that will work on any system. My problem with it is more around the lack of companies using it.</description></item><item><title>dbv Alpha Release</title><link>https://www.jamestombleson.com/posts/2022/12/28/dbv-alpha-release/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 21:21:30 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.jamestombleson.com/posts/2022/12/28/dbv-alpha-release/</guid><description>So, last month one of my Linux servers failed and I was unable to recover the VM. I was lucky that the data cared about stored on a mobile device! Of my containers, the one running my webdav instance was the one I didnt want to lose any data. With that scare, I wanted to address my backup solution, or lack of. So one thing I wanted to do was build a new tool to backup my docker data.</description></item><item><title>2023 Goals</title><link>https://www.jamestombleson.com/posts/2022/12/27/2023-goals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 18:11:30 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.jamestombleson.com/posts/2022/12/27/2023-goals/</guid><description>As we roll into 2023 I have some new goals that I am working on.
1. Start Blogging One of the things I have seen is people talk about learning in public. This is something I have not done too much right now. Sure you can find my GitHub profile and see what I am up to, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a roadmap per-say. So, time to start working on it.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://www.jamestombleson.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 15:57:20 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.jamestombleson.com/projects/</guid><description>Code Projects Newsbot Newsbot is my passion project to create your own personal news feed. This build around letting people run their own instance. Don&amp;rsquo;t let other services monitor what you pay attention to.
newsbot.portal This is the web interface to Newsbot. Built with Go. newsbot.collector.api This API collects the news found on the internet dvb (Docker Volume Backup) repo
This tool was made to backup my docker data given I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to chain a bunch of bash commands together.</description></item><item><title>Resume/CV</title><link>https://www.jamestombleson.com/resume/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 15:57:20 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.jamestombleson.com/resume/</guid><description>Experience DevOps Manager - Suddath Van Lines, Inc Systems Engineer - Special Counsel DevOps Engineer - Directors Mortgage IT Specialist, Contract - Georgia Pacific Systems Administrator - Remedi Senior Care IT Specialist - Rural Alaska Community Action Program Education Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) in Computer Networking Experience DevOps Manager - Suddath Van Lines, Inc Location: Remote
When: February 2021 - Present
Saved the company money on the Azure bill by 30% with in-depth review of our utilization and removed waste.</description></item><item><title>Test</title><link>https://www.jamestombleson.com/posts/test/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 15:57:20 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.jamestombleson.com/posts/test/</guid><description>This is a test blog, did I work???</description></item></channel></rss>